[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This defect of Earths atmosphere, caused by industrial pollution, lets more radiation reach the surface of our planet.", "correct_answer": "The Ozone Hole", "incorrect_answers": ["The Greenhouse Hole", "The Smoke Hole", "Smog Tear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Joe Dirt, what event made Joe remember his real last name?", "correct_answer": "He was flung around by an alligator.", "incorrect_answers": ["He got beat up.", "He had a brain operation.", "He got hit in the head by a door."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Germany?", "correct_answer": "Berlin", "incorrect_answers": ["Frankfurt", "Munich", "Hamburg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie was NOT released in theaters around the same time the 1989 movie UHF was?", "correct_answer": "Hook", "incorrect_answers": ["Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade", "Batman", "Lethal Weapon 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What period marks the beginning of extensive land colonization by plants?", "correct_answer": "Devonian", "incorrect_answers": ["Cretaceous", "Cambrian", "Permian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Modern cars pollute much less than cars did in the 60s. Today, it takes this many modern cars to produce the same amount of air pollution as a car from the 60s.", "correct_answer": "20", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "10", "35"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What member of  the classic Our Gang comedies had a bit part in the movie Its a Wonderful Life?", "correct_answer": "Alfalfa", "incorrect_answers": ["Darla", "Spanky", "Buckwheat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these U.S. cities did the first worldwide Monopoly championship take place?", "correct_answer": "New York", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago", "Washington DC", "Las Vegas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country was formerly known as the Republic of Upper Volta. On August 4, 1984, President Thomas Sankara gave it a new name which means the land of upright people.", "correct_answer": "Burkina Faso", "incorrect_answers": ["Burundi", "Kyrgyzstan", "Djibouti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Shrek use as a candle in the first Shrek movie?", "correct_answer": "His ear wax buildup", "incorrect_answers": ["His finger", "A snake", "Donkeys tail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the actress who provides the voice of Ellie from Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs?", "correct_answer": "Queen Latifah", "incorrect_answers": ["Angelina Jolie", "Cameron Diaz", "Julia Roberts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Just before Bill gets killed in Friday the 13th, he is walking along the lake and whistling. What is the number on the jersey he is wearing?", "correct_answer": "88", "incorrect_answers": ["81", "86", "94"]}]